Guide to the Seymour L. Green, compiler, genealogy, 1955-1968.
Green, Seymour L. (compiler, genealogy), 1955-1968.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Seymour L. Green, compiler, genealogy, 1955-1968.
1946
Seymour L. Green.
.4 cubic ft.
Genealogies, memoranda, biographical sketches, obituaries, a photograph, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
"Genealogy of Descendants of William Green (1754-1835) and Temperence (Heatley) Green (1760-1822)"; typescript copies of memoranda written by Henry Green, son of William and Temperance, concerning the lives of various members of the Heatley family and their relatives in America, the British Isles, and India; and biographical sketches and obituaries of John Arbuthnot Green, Jr., William Wilkinson Green, and Morris Miller Green. Also, a typescript copy of the Valedictory Oration of Morris S. Miller at Union College in 1798; photograph of Heatley Green; Miller family genealogy by Blandina Dudley Miller; and other genealogical materials on members of the related Miller, Green, and Heatley families.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
"Genealogy of Descendants of William Green (1754-1835) and Temperence (Heatley) Green (1760-1822)"; typescript copies of memoranda written by Henry Green, son of William and Temperance, concerning the lives of various members of the Heatley family and their relatives in America, the British Isles, and India; and biographical sketches and obituaries of John Arbuthnot Green, Jr., William Wilkinson Green, and Morris Miller Green. Also, a typescript copy of the Valedictory Oration of Morris S. Miller at Union College in 1798; photograph of Heatley Green; Miller family genealogy by Blandina Dudley Miller; and other genealogical materials on members of the related Miller, Green, and Heatley families.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Green, Seymour L.; Green family.; Green, Heatley.; Green, John Arbuthnot, Jr.; Green, Morris Miller.; Green, Temperance Heatley, 1760-1822.; Green, William Wilkinson.; Green, William, 1754-1835.; Heatley family.; Miller family.; Miller, Blandina Dudley.; Miller, Morris S.
Places:
Great Britain--Genealogy.; India--Genealogy.
Form and Genre Terms:
Genealogies.; Obituraries.; Photographs.; Speeches.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Black looseleaf notebook
  - Section I.
    - "Genealogy of Descendants of William Green (1754-1835) and Temperance (Heatley) Green (1760-1822) 16 pp. (Box 1)
  - Section II. Typescript copies of Genealogical and Biographical Sketchesand Obituaries, made by CRH staff, as follows: (39 pp.)
    - 1. "Memos. Respecting the Progenitors of our Family by 'Henry Green, [son of above William and Temperance],'" 13 pp. (Box 1)
    - 2. John A. Green Sketch, 1 p. + footnotes. (Box 1)
    - 3. "Death of W.W. Green" - "Honors to a Former Syracusan" - "The Prize Essay," 5 pp. (Box 1)
    - 4. Tentative Obituary of Morris Miller Green, 1 p. (Box 1)
    - 5. Biographical sketch of M.M.G., 3 pp. (Box 1)
    - 6. Autobiographical sketch of M.M.G., 1934, 6 pp. (Box 1)
    - 7. Autobiographical sketch of M.M.G., 1934, 6 pp. (Box 1)
    - 8. Obituary of M.M.G., 1870-1955, 3 p. (Box 1)
    - 9. Brief sketches of Morris Smith Miller (1814-1870) and Morris S. Miller (1779-1824) from Herringshaw's. (Box 1)
- Valedictory oration of Morris S. Miller at Union College in 1798. (Box 1)
- Green, Miller and Heatley Family Genealogies, 1698-1960; .05 ft. 1/2" typescript and photocopies. (Box 1)
- Green, Miller and Heatley Families. Genealogy, ca. 1968 (biog. sheet on Andrew Heatley Green). (Box 1)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Photo of H. Green in Archives Picture Collection.
Letter from Baron von Steuben (d. 1794), New York, Mar. 12 [1794?], to Peter Smith, Old Fort Schuyler, stating thathe has sold 6000 acres of the northern part of his patent at 16/- per acre, but that he does not plan to sell any more land at present, and discussing other business matters. Placed in #1607, Peter Smith papers, Mss. file.
Agreement, signed by M.R. Bleecker, Peter Brinckerhoff, and Charles Dudley, Albany, Feb. 23, 1810, whereby Morris S. Miller is to receive out of the joint funds one thousand dollars as compensation for attending to the joint concerns of the signatories. Presumably refers to Bleecker interest in Cosby's Manor. Transferred to #1942.